Hi!
On our next segment, I'm going to be showing lip liner application.
When applying lip liner, our clients tend to make the same mistake.
That mistake is to actually start our application from here and go down.
What that's going to do is it's going to cut off the lips.
If we were to start from the corner and go up, we almost always never give up the integrity of the shape.
That's the technique we're going to follow today.
A lot of time lip liner gets left far behind, but the amazing part about lip liner is that it's long wearing.
It also creates a definition that's going to last all day.
Sometimes if you just apply lip liner, you can just apply gloss throughout the day and it's going to keep that shape on the lips.
For brides, a lot of times I'll actually use the lip liner as lip stick.
Because it is so long wearing or a little bit dryer on the lips, it deposits that pigment very deep.
Our first step is to of course choose our pigment.
Because we went with a little bit more smokey eye, we're going to go with a little bit subtle lip.
I'm actually going to start on the corner here and I'm going to work my way up just sort of feathering in.
Now, just doing a very dramatic line up, again, you're going to lose that intergrity of the lip and then follow that lower line just to create a little bit of definition.
Again, if you were creating that long wearing effect, at this point you could go ahead and apply all over the lip.
Watch our next segment on applying lip color.